FEDIMAR KAYL RABANZO

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

frabanzoo@gmail.com +63-976-040-9290 github.com/kayl06 https://findkaylrabanzo.vercel.app

Skilled full-stack web developer with 4 years of experience designing, developing, and deploying enterprise-level applications. Proficient in multiple programming languages, software development methodologies, and database management systems. Strong problem-solving skills and ability to work effectively in a team-based or individual environment.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Playasia

Web Developer • 2022 - Present

- Maintain and enhance an e-commerce website, and admin system.
- Integrate new functions and features to meet client goals and enhance internal efficiency.
- Planned, designed, developed, and maintained both the front-end and back-end of the e-commerce website and admin system.
- Understand client requirements and business needs, and plan the development of systems and applications accordingly.
- Provide technical support via calls or chats and offer assistance to the internal team as needed.
- Proactively identify issues and improvement opportunities, and communicate findings through appropriate channels.
- Collaborate with the product team or CEO to brainstorm and create new features
- Discover and fix programming bugs to ensure smooth application functionality.
- Protect business operations by maintaining the confidentiality of information.
- Optimize applications for maximum speed, scalability, and performance.

Dunbrae Subic Incorporated

Full Stack Web Developer • 2020 - 2022

- Conducted meetings with the president and managers to discuss project requirements and workflow.
- Implemented new functions, features, and development techniques in the production process to achieve client goals, creative objectives, and enhance internal efficiencies.
- Collaborated with the Team Lead and President to brainstorm and create client web application systems.
- Designed and implemented a custom <u>Customer Satisfaction Survey</u> with employee dashboards.
- Executed the design for new websites or the reconstruction of existing ones.
- Implemented third-party APIs (e.g., 7/11 API) to automate manual processes.
- Planned, designed, and developed in-house websites from layout to function, aligning with business specifications.
- Provided assistance to the team for data integration and system programming.
- Identified and resolved programming bugs to ensure the smooth functionality of applications.
- Studied information needs, system flow, data usage, and work processes to improve efficiency.
- Protected operations by maintaining confidentiality of information.

SKILLS

Web Design, Front-end coding, Back-End Coding, User Interface/User Experience, Design Thinking, Custom Databases, Mobile App Development, API Integration.

Programming Languages

JavaScript (ES6+), PHP, Web API / REST API, MySQL, OOP, MVC, TypeScript, HTML5, CSS3, Sass, JSON, SOLID.

Frameworks & Libraries

ReactJS, Redux, NextJS, Express.js, Node.js, TailwindCSS, Axios, JQuery, Codelgniter4, Laravel, Ionic3, Ionic4, Angular 8, Bootstrap

Tools & Platforms

VisualStudio Code, PHPStorm, Netlify, Vercel, WordPress, Figma, Git, GitHub, GitLab, SourceTree, Knowledgeable in Docker

SELECTED PROJECTS

Pariserve

Parish Event Scheduling Web and Mobile Application.

sophia.play-asia.com

A landing page for client merch built with HTML, CSS and JavaScript

Themes Template

HTML/CSS Theme Template built with React JS

Only Sweater

E-commerce website using TypeScript-ReactJS

findkaylrabanzo.vercel.app

Personal website built with NextJS and ReactJS

IDESS Interactive Technologies

Junior Full Stack Web Developer • 2019 - 2020

- Ensured brand consistency by overseeing adherence to guidelines in all online content, including e-Learning materials and computer-based testing tools.
- Collaborated with the team to analyze pre-project plans and assess technical requirements, developing functioning and user-friendly computer interfaces aligned with business goals.
- Migrate and upgrade the old system to the new and modern design system.
- Analyzed, designed, and developed websites according to business/client needs.
- Executed the design for new websites or the reconstruction of existing ones, maintaining alignment with brand and business objectives.
- Implemented online synchronization between web applications and desktop applications, enhancing accessibility and user experience.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Gordon College • 2017-2019

Associate in Computer Technology

Gordon College • 2015-2017

CERTIFICATIONS

MODERN REACT AND REDUX

Udemy • 2023